TAHA ASIF



Contact



Address

3955 Zenith Court Mississauga, Ontario L5N 7H7



Phone

(416) 859-8242



Email

taha2456@gmail.com

Core Competencies

- Brand Management
- Project Management
- Interpersonal Skills
- Complex Problem Resolver
- Distribution/Inventory Control
- Strategic Planning
- Client Relations
- Multi-Task/Prioritize Effectively
- Product Launch
- Product Management
- Promotion Strategy
- Training Facilitation
- Advertising Strategy
- Leadership
- Quality Control

Skills

Management

Brand Management
Product Launches
Customer Relationship
Management
Event Management
Project Management
Human Resource

MARKETING MANGER - MARKETING MANAGEMENT

Five + years of work experience within the experiential marketing industry as an event/program manager, client relations manager and field manager representing clients such as Blackberry Ubisoft, Warner Bros, Samsung Motorola, Apple, and Paramount Pictures. Roles have involved conducting market research to determine market requirements for existing and future products, productivity of marketing plans and projects to ensure maximum efficiency of client's objectives and outcome. Recognized as a leader and strengths in analysis of customer research, current market conditions and competitor information over the years for executing successful product launches, brand events, in-store demos along with in-field product support along with key data analysis, tracking and monitoring to ensure all sales/client objectives are going beyond their expectations.

EDUCATION 2010

University of Guelph-Humber, Toronto, Ontario

Bachelor Degree in Business Administration

2010

Major: International Business and Marketing

Dual Diploma and Degree designation program from the University of Guelph and Humber College

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance (Various Companies) - Toronto, ON

Field Marketing Manager/Program Manager

SEPT 2009 - PRESENT

- Represented companies such as Match Marketing Inventa, GMR, Diamond Marketing, ThinkPoint Communications (U.S. Based), Encore Nationwide (U.S. Based), The Hype Agency (U.S. Based) GT-Events (U.S.Based) and Consumer Impact Marketing
- Clients included: Warner Bros, Rogers, Nike, Blackberry, Microsoft, Samsung, Dell, Coca Cola, FIFA, CIBC, Nintendo, Xbox

Amazon Canada - Mississauga, ON

Corporate Recruiter

OCT 2011 - JAN 2012

- Responsible with staffing for the newly opened Amazon Warehouse in the warehouse district in Mississauga
- Synergized the on-boarding process of approximately 1,000 warehouse workers along with seasonal temporary workers
- Ensured safety protocols and procedures were being met on a daily basis which has kept for a accident-free workplace environment
- Reduced the attrition rate by 15% with continued support and encouragement along with incentive programs for new employees

APR 2011 - OCT 2011

Achievo Corporation – Toronto, ON

Sales and Marketing Coordinator

- Specializing in areas of application development, QA testing and IT Service Management
- Supported existing channel relationships by coordinating with vendor sales and marketing contacts
- Coordinated Request For Proposal (RFP) submissions, both internally and externally with client's contacts, Coordinated participation at marketing events